Maybe I forgot
Forgot
Boss
I've been too tired these days
Mixing the feed
Feeding them
Checking the water temperature
Doing the work of three people
Isn't it normal to forget
a couple of times
Anyway these little beasts
Won't die from starving for a couple days
What kind of attitude is that
Can't you tell my attitude
Boss
I've been at this farm for a while now
Mixing feeding checking temperature
and logging data
I do all this work by myself
To be brutally honest
The reason these frogs
are doing so well
Is all thanks to me Jason
To tell you the truth
Daniel across the street said
He offered me 30000 a month
to work for him
That's three times what you pay me
Let me be clear today
Either you raise my salary
To 30000
Not a penny less
Or I leave right now
Suit yourself
The salary I give you
Is already the highest in the industry
Then there's nothing more to say
All your skills
I taught you myself
And based on your current work
It's not worth 30000
If Daniel is offering you that much
He definitely has an ulterior motive
Careful not to end up empty-handed
You just can't stand to see me do well
Why are you packing Jason
I quit
Lewes
You just got lucky
Becoming the boss
What gives you the right
to look down on me
You're making my life miserable
So I'll make yours miserable too
I'm going across the street
To work at Boss Daniel's farm
Why
Boss Lewes pays pretty well here
And pays social security
Other places only pay two or three thousand
With no insurance
Yeah
Boss Lewes helped us all out
The food here is good too
Meat at every meal
When it's not busy we get to rest
And he doesn't say anything
He's a very good boss
You've all been tricked by him